callsource.com 2019-05-18

# CallSource's Privacy Policy to protect online users' privacy

### Privacy Policy

##### Effective Date: October 20, 2017

_We are committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below._

This “Privacy Policy” discloses the privacy practices governing our knowing collection, use, and disclosure of information. Capitalized terms shall have the meaning designated in the CallSource Networks Terms of Service located at https://www.callsource.com/legal/msa/, unless specifically defined in this Privacy Policy. All references herein to “we” or “us” refer to CallSource® (“CallSource”). All references to the “site” refer to our website located at <https://www.callsource.com/>. All references to the “service” refer to our platforms: CallTrack® and Results®.

###### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY

Our Site is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through the Site.

###### WHAT WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

INFORMATION RELATED TO DATA COLLECTED FOR OUR CLIENTS WHEN WE ARE OPERATING AS A DATA PROCESSOR

CallSource collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly.

CallSource may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to these third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

CallSource has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the CallSource’s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests CallSource to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

###### PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Although you may generally use our site without providing us with any personally identifiable information, for some site applications or services, we may collect certain types of personally identifiable information, including: name, postal address, e-mail addresses, and phone number. This type of information is only collected from you voluntarily; we will never gather or store such information without your knowledge and consent. Examples of where we might gather such information from you: when you sign up to receive e-mail updates or newsletters about the site, our products, or services; to allow you to register or update your individual profile on the site; to help personalize the site for you; or to allow you to provide feedback, or ask a question. In some situations, you will need to provide some or all of the above-described personally identifiable information in order for certain personalized features of the site to function properly (e.g., accessing the partner program portals).

When you provide such information for a specific purpose, such as receiving product alerts, we will use such information to contact you solely for that purpose, except that we may at times also contact you to provide you with critical site information that impacts the features, product information, or services you have requested.

We do not share personally identifiable information collected at this site with third parties, except for the limited instances noted below. The exceptions are:

  1. We may share your information with our agents who assist us in administering the site and various programs and promotions. They can only use the information to administer our site, services, and products. These agents are required to keep your information private and secure.
  2. If you opt-in (either at the time of providing personally identifiable information, or at a later time) to have us share your information with our partners for the purpose of receiving information from our partners and other companies.
  3. We may also disclose personally identifiable information if we are required to comply with laws, or if in our good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights of CallSource®, its customers and the public.
  4. In the event of an acquisition of all or part of CallSource® by another company, or in the event that CallSource® were to sell or dispose of all or a part of the CallSource® business, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by CallSource®, which could include personally identifiable information, subject to applicable law. Similarly, information may be transferred as part of a reorganization or insolvency proceeding.
  5. We may on occasion combine information we receive with outside records or site usage information to enhance our consumer profiles for our own marketing and development purposes (in accordance with this Privacy Policy).

###### COOKIE/TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

This site may use cookie and tracking technology. A “Cookie,” is a tiny file that your browser places on your computer’s hard drive, which acts to identify your computer. Cookie and cookie tracking technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help tailor the site to visitors’ needs and help customize the site for visitors. For example, we may use cookies to store your site preferences, usage patterns, and other information so that the site will function better for you on subsequent visits. The site may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other similar purposes. Personally identifiable information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information (as discussed above), cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregated cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. If you choose to reject the site’s cookies, some areas of the site may not function properly or may not be accessible.

###### AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED LOG INFORMATION

In addition to the information discussed above, when you visit the site we may collect and store the following information in our logs for each browser request. We may use such information for development and marketing purposes (we will not use IP addresses externally except as set forth above).

  1. the date and time
  2. the originating IP address
  3. the type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser)
  4. the URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
  5. the object requested
  6. completion status of the request
  7. pages visited

###### INFORMATION PROCESSING

We process information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners, provided that we will not reveal such information except in accordance with this privacy policy.

###### DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION AND SURVEYS AND POLLS

We may ask for demographic or profile (age, gender, household, interests, etc.) information in a survey/poll or at registration. This information is used to assist us in tailoring the site, our communications, and our services and products to visitors and consumers. We may share aggregated demographic and survey information, as opposed to individual information, with third parties. You always have the option of not responding to any questionnaire, survey, or poll.

###### SECURITY, OPTING OUT, AND ACCESS TO INFORMATION

CallSource uses commercially reasonable efforts to keep personally identifiable information secure. When you enter sensitive information (such as billing information or login credentials) within our platform, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Only authorized CallSource employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information and only to help CallSource administer its promotional programs and the site. If you have any questions regarding security you can contact us at <https://www.callsource.com/contact/>.

If you have signed up to participate in our partner programs or receive newsletters and email from us, we will make every effort to have all such communications allow you to opt-out of further such communications. To otherwise unsubscribe from our mailing list(s) or opt-out of receiving communications from CallSource, you can always follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the emails you receive or email us at <https://www.callsource.com/contact/>. If you have provided us with your consent to share your personal information with our third party partners and wish to have your information no longer used you may notify us via email to marketingdepartment@callsource.com.

If enabled on the site, you may visit your account settings page to delete your account and/or information. You can also contact us at <https://www.callsource.com/contact/> to access your information, amend any inaccuracies or request deletion of your account and/or information. Please note that any information that we have from your or that we process on your behalf may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request. This may be the case even though no information about your account remains in our active user databases. Also please note that log files are not affected by account deletion requests.

###### GENERAL

Third party Internet sites accessible through hyperlinks from this site have their own privacy practices, and CallSource has no responsibility or liability for these independent practices. Please review their privacy practices.

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a prominent notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

###### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions about our services or Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://www.callsource.com/contact/).
